<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coding. on Sören Schmidt-Clausen</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/</link><description>Recent content in Coding. on Sören Schmidt-Clausen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blender Workflow Addons</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/blender_addons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/blender_addons/</guid><description>While doing my internship at Faber Courtial I created some addons for blender, to connect blender more easily into the studio workflow. 3 of them I was allowed to release to the public.
EasyAutomation Source Code
A simple addon to ease the automation and scripting workflow in blender. It allows you to expose variables of your python script and run them from the 3d viewport. I created it, so you could make exports of unconvetional objects easier by defining a custom script for it.</description></item><item><title>Dummy Joyride</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/dummy_joyride/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/dummy_joyride/</guid><description>A school project from the 11th grade, in which I designed and created a Java game together with 3 other students. We were inspired by the mobile game &amp;ldquo;Jetpack-Joyride&amp;rdquo;. The game logic and most of the textures are from me.</description></item><item><title>Pacman</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/pacman/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/pacman/</guid><description>My own version of Pacman, which I developed in my spare time in the Java programming language. For the basic logic I used my own engine, which I developed especially for this game.</description></item><item><title>Virus Controller</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/virus_controller/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/coding/virus_controller/</guid><description>A game I made with a friend for a game jam. In the game you play an anti-virus program and have to shoot down the virus dots. If you succeed, new windows are created on which you can walk around. Meanwhile the virus dots try to destroy the windows so you fall down.</description></item></channel></rss>