<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Short Films on Sören Schmidt-Clausen</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/</link><description>Recent content in Short Films on Sören Schmidt-Clausen</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Laptop becomes alive</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/laptop_becomes_alive/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/laptop_becomes_alive/</guid><description>A funny thought &amp;hellip;
Story It&amp;rsquo;s about a little laptop that comes to life and also can walk. He breaks out of the house and runs out into the world. In the evening, he comes across a shop window that shows people destroying machines. This makes him very angry.
Animation For the animation I used several so-called constraints. With them you can set certain conditions on objects in Blender. For example, that the foot always points in the direction of the holder, which is similar to the behavior of a gear.</description></item><item><title>Black Hole Animation</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/black_hole_animation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/black_hole_animation/</guid><description>As a fan of the Netflix series &amp;ldquo;Lost in Space&amp;rdquo; I tried to model the spaceship &amp;ldquo;Jupiter&amp;rdquo;. I also wanted to make a small animation and this short film was the result.
Story The story is relatively short. You see a spaceship (Jupiter) flying into a portal and reappearing near a black hole. There it has lost control and is pulled into it. The whole thing is ends in a bluescreen.</description></item><item><title>Naturalism Explainer Video</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/naturalism_explainer_video/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/naturalism_explainer_video/</guid><description>For the German class in the 11th grade we were supposed to make an explanatory video about literature era. Together with a buddy we made a video about naturalism. We thought it would be a fun idea to film the whole thing in Minecraft. This allowed us to choose the location freely, because we just had to build them to use them.
Story The explanatory video shows me &amp;ldquo;Sören&amp;rdquo;, who starts his paper on naturalism much too late and rushes to a library.</description></item><item><title>Computer sciene explainer video</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/info_explain_video/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/info_explain_video/</guid><description>For my 11th grade computer science class, I was asked to make a StopMotion movie explaining a principle of computer science. I decided to make a dramatic production with Lego.
Story The story is about a robot that gets an order from the user to remove an element at the beginning of a list. The robot accepts this command and calls the first element of the list (a person). It asks this element who is its successor (future first element).</description></item><item><title>Test: Failed</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/test_failed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/test_failed/</guid><description>A little thought experiment that I wanted to explore in a short video.
Story It&amp;rsquo;s about the idea about what would happen if you plug the power cable of a multi-plug into yourself. The cable starts to glow and it seems to work for the time being. But then all energy disappears and the earth has no more electricity. Maybe even the whole universe?</description></item><item><title>Robots in Love</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/robots_in_love/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/robots_in_love/</guid><description>For art class, we were asked to create a work on the theme &amp;ldquo;Together we are strong&amp;rdquo;. The medium wasn&amp;rsquo;t specified. Because of my experience with Blender, I thought about creating a 3D animated short film.
Story The short film is about two robots. At the beginning you only see a blue one (symbol for a man). He wakes up and discovers a silver sphere. On the way to it he has a flashback, how he meets a purple (symbol for a woman) robot.</description></item><item><title>Melon Movie</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/melon_movie/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/melon_movie/</guid><description>My biggest project so far. I worked on it for a total of 1 year.
Story The story is about a melon. In the beginning, it is carried to different places by an unknown force. It eventually finds itself in a refrigerator. From there, it breaks out a small piece of itself that explores the world. On its journey it admires: a drop of water, birds, a garage and a forest.</description></item><item><title>Lama Short</title><link>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/lamma_short/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://soerensc.xyz/work/shorts/lamma_short/</guid><description>The lama short film (title yet to be determined) is my current project that I have been working on since the winter of 2021. The lama is a 3D scan of a real llama stuffed animal. For this, I took around 350 photos of the stuffed animal in good lighting conditions. For this it was important to capture all possible perspectives.
Story The story is about a lama that is asleep at first.</description></item></channel></rss>